Finding Aid for Rensis Likert papers, 1929-1983.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Bureau of Agricultural Economics
  - Reports and memoranda
    - 1943
      - Farmers' Attitudes Toward Various Types of Farm Laborers: Cumberland County, New Jersey and Hartford County, Connecticut, Study No. A-3; Report No. C-15, 2/23/1943 (Box 1, Folder 51)
      - Memorandum concerning the distribution and display of Government posters in business establishments, 2/23/1943 (Box 1, Folder 51)
      - Farmers' Attitudes Toward The Use of Japanese Evacuees as Farm Labor, Part II: Five Major Crop Regions, Study A/3; Report No. C-16, 2/27/1943 (Box 1, Folder 52)
      - An Exploratory Study of Attitudes Towards Buying and Shortages of Consumer Goods, Study 62; Report No, 3/01/1943 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Public Responses to the Mileage Rationing Program: In Cleveland and Clark County, Ohio. Study 61, Report No. 37, 3/03/1943 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Farmers' Attitudes Toward Various Types of Farm Laborers. Irrigated Areas of the West. Study A/3, Report No. C-17, 3/04/1943 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - An Exploratory Study of Attitudes Towards Buying and Shortages of Consumer Goods, Study 62; Report No. 38, 3/05/1943 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Attitudes of Farmers Influencing Dairy Production for 1943 Study A-6, Report No. C-19, 3/12/1943 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Farmers' Attitudes Toward Various Types of Farm Laborers, The Midwest Area, Study A-3; Report No. C-18, 3/17/1943 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Attitudes of Farmers Regarding Dairy Production in 1943 Study A-6; Report No. C-19, 3/19/1943 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Memorandum: Attitudes of Iowa and Illinois Farmers Toward Farm Prices, 3/30/1943 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Memorandum: concerning certain Psychological Considerations in the Problem of Differential Rationing, 3/30/1943 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Extracts from Interviews with Farmers in Iowa and Illinois, Study 60, from Report No. 39, 4/14/1943 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Avoiding a Land Boom, 4/1943 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Rural Bond Sales in Iowa and Illinois, Study 60, Report No. 39, 4/06/1943 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Memorandum: Attitudes of Iowa and Illinois Farmers Toward Farm Prices, 4/07/1943 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Field Observations on the Western Iowa, Northern Illinois, Wisconsin, Minnesota and South Dakota Farm Front, 4/13/1943 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Farmers' Attitudes Toward Various Types of Farm Laborers: Summary Charts, 4/15/1943 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Memorandum: Field Observations on the Eastern Nebraska Farm Area, 4/17/1941
      - Fear of Non-Redemption of War Bonds, Study 65, Report No. 40, 4/16/1943 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - The Effect of Quotas on the Sale of War Bonds, Study 65; Report No. 41, 4/29/1943 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Memorandum to Fuel Oil Rationing Branch, O.P.A, concerning Preliminary Report of Survey of Public Responses to the Fuel Oil Rationing Program, 4/29/1943 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Extracts /from Interviews with Farmers in Iowa and Illinois, Study 60 Supplement, 5/14/1943 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Public Experience with Fuel Oil Rationing. Study 66; Report No. 42, 5/22/1943 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Public Experience with Fuel Oil Rationing, Study 66; Background files, 5/22/1943 (Box 2, Folder 9a)
      - Reasons People Give for and Against Buying Bonds, Study 65; Report No. 43, 6/03/1943 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - The Sale of War Bonds in Urban Areas, Study 65; Report No. 44, 6/04/1943 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Public Experience with Fuel Oil Rationing in Boston, New York City, Detroit, Chicago--Study 66; Report No. 45, 6/10/1943 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Memorandum to Fuel Oil Rationing Branch, O.P.A, concerning Observations regarding the response to fuel oil rationing, 6/09/1943 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - An Appraisal of the Second War Loan Drive: Identification and Motivation (Preliminary Tabulations), Study 68, 6/14/1943 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Memorandum: A Comparison of Frequency Distributions Obtained in Two Surveys Conducted for the Treasury Department, 6/15/1943 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Corn Belt Farmers' Attitude Toward the Production of Soybeans and Corn, Study 87, 6/15/1943 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Memorandum: Complaints about Various Rationing Programs, 6/16/1943 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - An Appraisal of the Second War Loan Drive Identification and Motivation: A comparison of Farm and Non/Farm Populations (Preliminary Tabulations), study 68, 6/23/1943 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - An Appraisal of the Second War Loan Drive, Participation and Implementation, Study 68; Report No. 46, 7/08/1943 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Winter Vegetable Scouting Survey, 7/10/1943 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Plans and Attitudes of Winter Vegetable Growers in the Imperial Valley, 7/12/1943 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Plans and Attitudes of Winter Vegetable Growers in Palm Beach and Broward Counties, Florida, 7/21/1943 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - Plans and Attitudes of Winter Vegetable Growers in Los Angeles County, 7/22/1943 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - An Appraisal of the Second War Loan (Summary Report), Study 68; Report No. 47, 7/26/1943 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - Plans and Attitudes of Winter Vegetable Growers in Monterey County, California, 7/31/1943 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - Ration Holders Talk About Last Year's Fuel Oil Program, 8/1943 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Farmers at Work in Wartime, 8/1943 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - The Land Market: Farmer and Landlord Opinion Concerning a Possible Boom and Its Control, Study 69; Report No. 48, 8/05/1943 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - An Appraisal of the Second War Loan Drive Identification and Motivation, Study 68 Report No. 49, 8/09/1943 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - The Current Livestock Feed Situation, Study 67, Report No. 50, 8/09/1943 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - Nutrition Practices in Two Selected Communities, Study 70, 8/19/1943 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Public Experience with Wartime Food Restrictions in Two Selected Communities, Memorandum--General Conclusions, 9/04/1943 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - The Attitudes and Problems of Peanut Growers in the Cross Timbers Area of Oklahoma, 2/18/1943 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - The Land Market: Opinions of Community Centers of Interest Toward a Possible Boom and its Control, Study 69; Report No. 52, 9/08/1943 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - The Community Program in Peoria, 9/09/1943 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - The Land Market Part II: Opinions of Corn Belt Realtors, Bankers, and Government Officials Toward a Possible Boom and its Control, Study 69; Report No. 69, 9/20/1943 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - The Attitudes and Problems of Peanut Growers in the Cross Timbers Area of Oklahoma, 9/20/1943 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - Public Experience with Wartime Food Scarcities in Two Selected Communities Part IV: Nutrition Practices, Study 70; Report No. 70, 9/22/1943 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - Public Experience with Wartime Food Scarcities in Two Selected Communities Part I: Changes in Food Habits, Study 70; Report No. 70, 9/24/1943 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Industrial Nutrition: Worker Responses to Community and In-plant Nutritional Programs in: 1. Peoria, Illinois; 2. Evansville, Indiana, Study 72, 9/24/1943 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Attitudes of Midwest Farmers Toward Soybean Production, 9/29/1943 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Attitudes of the American People Toward International Affairs, 9/30/1943 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Public Experience with Wartime Food Restrictions in Two Selected Communities Part I: Changes in Food Habits, Study 70; Report No. 70, lo/01/1943 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Public Experience with Wartime Food Restrictions in Two Selected Communities Part II: Attitudes Toward War Food Programs, Study 70; Report No. 70, 10/01/1943 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Public Experience with Wartime Food Restrictions in Two Selected Communities Part III: Factors Related to Acceptance or Resentment of Food Restrictions, Study 70; Report No. 70, 10/01/1943 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Public Experience with Wartime Food Restrictions in Two Selected Communities Part IV: Nutrition Knowledge and Practices Study 70; Report No. 70, 10/01/1943 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Public Experience with Wartime Food Restrictions in Two Selected Communities Part V: Supplement: Three Specimen Interviews, Study 70; Report No. 70, 10/01/1943 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Outlook of the /American People toward Post-War Domestic Conditions, 10/01/1943 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Preliminary Northeast Dairy Report, 10/01/1943 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Attitudes of Midwest Farmers Toward Soybean Production, 10/05/1943 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Industrial Nutrition: 1. Worker Responses to Community and In-Plant Nutrition Programs II. Worker Estimations of In-Plant Cafeterias in Peoria, Illinois and Evansville, Indiana, Report No. 72-I and II, 10/06/1943 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Industrial Feeding, Memorandum: Nutritional Promotion among Industrial Workers, 10/15/1943 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - An Appraisal of the Third War Loan Drive Part I: Identification and Motivation (Preliminary Tabulations) Report No. 78-I, 10/18/1943 (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - Industrial Nutrition: III. Worker Responses to the Present Food Situation IV. Worker Information about Nutrition in Peoria, Illinois and Evansville, Indiana, Report No. 72/111 and IV, 10/18/1943 (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - An Appraisal of the Third War Loan Drive Part II: Identification and Motivation A Comparison of Farm and Non-Farm Populations (Preliminary Tabulations), Study 78-11, 10/26/1943
      - Corn and Livestock in the Cash-Corn Area, Report No. 75, 10/28/1943 (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Memorandum, 10/29/1943 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Nutrition and the War: Opinions about Food, and Their Significance for Better Nutrition, 11/1943 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Household Uses of Fats and Oils, 11/02/1943 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Trends of Thought Behind Farmers' Attitudes Toward the Milk Subsidy, 11/04/1943 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Milk Production: Attitudes of Northeast Dairy Farmers (Preliminary Report), Study 77-1, 11/05/1943 (Box 2, Folder 31)
      - Household Uses of Fats and Oils in Four Southern Counties (Preliminary Report), Study 79, 11/06/1943 (Box 2, Folder 32)
      - Public Experience with Wartime Food Restrictions in Two Selected Communities Part VI: Summary of Findings and Recommendations, Study 70; Report No. 70/VI, 11/06/1943 (Box 2, Folder 32)
      - A Survey Concerning the Redemption of Bonds, 11/06/1943 (Box 2, Folder 33)
      - Observations on the Farm Situation During October: Iowa and Southern Minnesota, 11/10/1943 (Box 2, Folder 33)
      - An Appraisal of the Third War Loan Drive Part III: Preliminary Analysis of Interviews with People who said They could not Afford to Buy Extra Bonds in September, Study 78-III, 11/11/1945 (Box 2, Folder 33)
      - Public Experience with Wartime Food, Restrictions in Two Selected Communities, Part VII. Selected Interviews with Food Retailers, Study 70; Report No. 70, 11/17/1943 (Box 2, Folder 34)
      - Household Uses of Fats and Oils: In Four Southern Counties, Report No. 79-1, 11/17/1943 (Box 2, Folder 34)
      - An Exploratory Study of Food/Retailer Experiences With the War Food Program in Selected Communities, 11/26/1943 (Box 2, Folder 34)
      - Public Experience with Shortages on the West Coast, 11/26/1943 (Box 2, Folder 35)
      - Bottle Necks in Milk Production: As Northeast Dairy Farmers See Them, Study 77-1, 11/27/1943 (Box 2, Folder 35)
      - Memorandum: Farmers' Reactions Toward Corn Prices, and Their Plans For 1944 Hog Production, 2/02/1943 (Box 2, Folder 36)
      - An Appraisal of the Third War Loan, Part IV Solicitation in the Third War Loan, Study 78/IV, 12/07/1943 (Box 2, Folder 36)
      - Bottle Necks in Milk Production: As Northeast Dairy Farmers See Them, Study 7-11, 12/08/1943 (Box 2, Folder 36)
      - Cornbelt Farmers' Opinions About Subsidies, 12/18/1943 (Box 2, Folder 37)
      - An Appraisal of the Third War Loan, Part V, Identification, Participation, and Motivation, Final Report; Study 78-V, 12/27/1943 (Box 2, Folder 37)
      - Use of Urban High School and College Students on Farms, 3/1943 (Box 23)
      - An Exploration into Some Problems of Inflation, Study E-1, 3, 3/09/1943 (Box 23)
      - The Farmers' Slant on Farm Labor, 4/6/1943 (Box 23)
      - "An Abridged Manual of Field Methods for Temporary Employees of the Division of Program Surveys" (Box 24)
      - Memorandum, "Public Attitudes Toward Inflation and Cost of Living" (Box 24)
      - "Work Improvement Program Work Training Manual" (Box 24)
    - 1944
      - Preliminary Summary: Effectiveness of the Potato Storage Campaign in Pittsburgh, 1/11/1944 (Box 2, Folder 37)
      - The Proposal to Remove Pork from the Ration: Reactions in a Small Iowa Town, 1/11/1944 (Box 2, Folder 37)
      - Corn and Hogs: The Observations of Corn Belt Farmers, Study 80-1, 1/11/1944 (Box 2, Folder 38)
      - Corn and Hogs. Study 80. Background file, 1/11/1944 (Box 2, Folder 38)
      - Preliminary Summary: Effectiveness of the Potato Storage Campaign in Pittsburgh, 1/12/1944 (Box 2, Folder 39)
      - Hog Production for 1944 The Plans and Observations of Corn Belt Farmers, Study 80-11, 1/20/1944 (Box 2, Folder 39)
      - The Potato Storage Campaign in Pittsburgh: Its Publicity and Effectiveness, study 84-1, 1/31/1944 (Box 2, Folder 39)
      - Public Reaction in Pittsburgh to Some Aspects of the Food Situation, 2/06/1944 (Box 2, Folder 40)
      - Housewives Discuss Nutrition Programs, Part I. Nutrition Meetings, Report No. 32-1, 2/14/1944 (Box 2, Folder 40)
      - Housewives Discuss Nutrition Programs. Study 82. Background files, 2/14/1944 (Box 2, Folder 40)
      - Farmers' Appraisal of Post-War Problems, 2/21/1944 (Box 2, Folder 41)
      - Farmers, Farm Prices, and Inflation: A Survey of Midwestern Dairy Farmers, (Summary Report) Study 83, 2/25/1944 (Box 2, Folder 41)
      - Farmers View the Postwar Period: Opinions of Farmers in the Corn Belt and Southeastern Cotton Regions--Highlights of the Findings (Preliminary Report), Study 85, 3/08/1944 (Box 2, Folder 42)
      - Farmers, Farm Prices, and Inflation: A Survey of Midwestern Dairy Farmers, Study 83--Full report, 3/09/1944 (Box 2, Folder 42)
      - Housewives Discuss Nutrition Programs, Part III: Supplemental Report, Study No. 82, 3/lo/1944 (Box 2, Folder 42)
      - Appraisal of the Fourth War Loan Drive, Part I: Identification, Motivation, and Participation (Preliminary Tabulations) Report No. 88-I, 3/15/1944 (Box 2, Folder 43)
      - Housewives Discuss Nutrition Programs, Part II: Radio and Publications, Report No. 82-II, 3/14/1944 (Box 2, Folder 43)
      - Housewives Discuss Nutrition Programs, Part III: Supplemental Report, Study No. 82, 3/14/1944 (Box 2, Folder 43)
      - Farmers, Farm Prices, and Inflation: A Survey of Midwestern Dairy Farmers, Study 83--Full report, 3/14/1944 (Box 2, Folder 44)
      - Memorandum to: Ralph Englesman, War Finance Division, 3/17/1944 (Box 2, Folder 44)
      - Appraisal of the Fourth War Loan Drive, Part II: Participation, Identification and Motivation among the Farm Population (Preliminary Tabulations), Report No. 88-II, 3/21/1944 (Box 2, Folder 44)
      - Appraisal of the Fourth War Loan Drive, Part II: Participation, Identification and Motivation among the Farm Population (Preliminary Tabulations), Report No. 88-II, 3/21/1944 (Box 2, Folder 45)
      - An Appraisal of the Fourth War Loan IV. Its Conduct and Results in Selected Plants, Study 88-IV, 3/28/1944 (Box 2, Folder 45)
      - An Appraisal of the Fourth War Loan, Part III: Solicitation in the Fourth War Loan, Study 88-III, 3/29/1944 (Box 2, Folder 45)
      - Housewives Discuss Nutrition Program: A Study in Bridgeport, Connecticut and Richmond, Virginia (Preliminary Report), 4/01/1944 (Box 2, Folder 46)
      - State Postwar Planning Reports and Farmers' Attitudes on Postwar Problems, 4/05/1944 (Box 2, Folder 46)
      - Appraisal of the Fourth War Loan Drive, Part V. A Study of Solicitore in a Large Urban Community, Report No. 88-v, 4/04/1944 (Box 2, Folder 46)
      - Appraisal of the Fourth War Loan Drive, Part IV: The Conduct and Results of the Drive in Selected Plants. Study 88-iv, 4/07/1944 (Box 2, Folder 46)
      - Bond Redemptions in March 1944 Study 93-I, 4/07/1944 (Box 2, Folder 47)
      - Farmers' Production Plans in 1944 Part I: Factors Determining Farmers' Crop Intentions, 4/08/1944 (Box 2, Folder 47)
      - Forward to the Fifth War Loan, 4/10/1944 (Box 2, Folder 47)
      - Appraisal of the Fourth War Loan Drive, Part IV: The Conduct and Results of the Drive in Selected Plants, Study 88-IV, 4/11/1944 (Box 2, Folder 47)
      - Appraisal of the Fourth War Loan Drive, Part I: Identification, Motivation, and Participation (Final Tabulations) Report No. 88-I (Revised), 4/19/1944 (Box 2, Folder 48)
      - Appraisal of the Fourth War Loan Drive, Part II: Participation, Identification and Motivation Among the Farm Population (Final Tabulations) Report No. 88-II. Revised, 4/21/1944 (Box 2, Folder 48)
      - Appraisal of the Fourth War Loan Drive, Part V: A Study of Solicitors in a Large Urban Community, Report No. 88-V., 4/22/1944 (Box 2, Folder 48)
      - Housewives Discuss Nutrition Programs: A Study in Bridgeport, Connecticut and Richmond, Virginia, 4/24/1944 (Box 2, Folder 49)
      - Housewives Discuss Nutrition Programs: A Study in Bridgeport, Connecticut and Richmond, Virginia, 5/1944 (Box 2, Folder 49)
      - Farmers' Attitudes and Information About Rationing and Price Control in Iowa, Wisconsin, Illinois and Indiana (Preliminary) Report No. 89, 5/02/1944 (Box 2, Folder 49)
      - Farmers' Production Plans in 1944 Part III: Machinery as a Factor in Farm Production Plans, Study 87-III, 5/15/1944 (Box 2, Folder 50)
      - What the Farmer Knows and Thinks of Price Control and Rationing: A Study of Four Midwestern States (Summary Report), Study No. 89-I, 5/15/1944 (Box 2, Folder 50)
      - Farmers' Production Plans in 1944 Part III: Machinery as a Factor in Farm Production Plans, Study 87-III, 5/22/1944 (Box 2, Folder 50)
      - Farmers View the Post/War World, Study 85-II, 5/26/1944 (Box 2, Folder 50)
      - What the Farmer Knows and Thinks of Price Control and Rationing: A Study of Four Midwestern States, Study No. 89-1, 5/26/1944 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - A Rumor About Bonds and the War, Report No. 88-VI, 5/29/1944 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - What the Farmer Knows and Thinks of Price Control and Rationing: A Study in Four Midwestern States, Study No. 89-II, Full Report, 5/31/1944 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Hired Farm Labor: in Three Dairy-Vegetable Areas of New York, Ohio and Illinois, Study No. 90, 5/31/1944 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Farmers' Production Plans in 1944 Part II Livestock Production: A Review of Farmers' Plans for their in 1944-1945 Livestock Production, Study 87-11, 6/13/1944 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Cattle Prospects in the Great Plains: Ranchers Size Up the Cattle Situation, Study No. 92, 6/17/1944 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Wartime Saving in Louisville, Study No. 94 Final Report, 6/21/1944 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Farmers' Reactions Toward the Corn Purchase Program: A Preliminary Report, study 96, 6/27/1944 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - The Marketing and Transportation Situation: Acceptance of Dehydrated Foods by Chicago Housewives, 7/1944 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Farmers View the Postwar World: Opinions of Farmers in the Cornbelt, the Southeastern Cotton Region, and the Central Valley of California, Study 85-VI, Final Report, 7/10/1944 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Prospects for Housewives' Use of Dehydrated Foods, Study 91-44, 7/12/1944 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - "Our War" in Bridgeport: Final Report, Study 99, 7/13/1944 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Consumer Response to Current Food Programs: A Study in Nine Metropolitan Areas--II. Current Interest in Food Information, Study 95-A, Part II, 7/22/1944 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Consumer Response to Current Food Programs A Study in Nine Metropolitan Areas--III. Experiences Since Point Reductions and Expectations of Future Rationing, Study 95-A, Part III, 7/22/1944 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Consumer Response to Current Food Programs: I. Response to Special War Food Programs Study 95-A, Part I, 7/27/1944 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - Preliminary Findings of Survey of Fifth War Loan with Special Reference to the Payroll Market, 7/30/1944 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Farmers' Production Plans in 1944--Part II Livestock Production: A Review of Farmers' Plans for their 1944-1945 Livestock Production, Study 87-11, 7/31/1944 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - The Land Market--Farmers' Opinions Concerning: The Present Land Market, Danger of a Land Boom, Desirability of Controls on the Land Market, Farming Opportunities for Returning Soldiers, Study 100, 8/01/1944 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Housewives Experiment with Dehydrated Eggs. Two Surveys in Chicago, Illinois, 8/01/1944 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - Farmers' Production Plans in 1944--Part IV Farm Labor Situation and Production Plans, Study 87-IV, 8/05/1944 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - Memorandum: Thinking Toward the Future in War Bond Publicity, 8/10/1944 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - The Corn Purchase Program: Reactions of Farmers in the Purchase Area, Final Report, study 96, 8/11/1944 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - Illustrative Quotations: From Interviews of the Fifth War Loan, Study 98, 8/12/1944 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Appraisal of the Fifth War Loan Drive--Part I Final Tabulations: Non-Farm Population, Report No. 98-1 (Revised), 8/13/1944 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - The Corn Purchase Program: Reactions of Farmers in the Purchase Area, Final Report, study 96, 8/16/1944 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - The Land Market - Farmers' Opinions Concerning: The present land market, Danger of a land boom, Desirability of controls on the land market, Farming opportunities for returning soldiers, Final Report, Study 100, 8/18/1944
      - Appraisal of the Fifth War Loan Drive--Part II: Farm Population, Final Tabulations, Study 98-II, 8/23/1944 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Farmers' Opinions About Post-War Conditions, Spring-Summer 1944; 9/04/1944 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Bank Solicitation in the Fifth War Loan, 9/06/1944 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Opinions About the Treasury's Fiscal Policy Held by a Special Sample of People in New York and Chicago, 9/09/1944 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Memorandum on Selling Bonds as the War Comes to an End, 9/19/1944 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Corn Belt Farmers Look at War Food Administration Programs (Preliminary Report), Study 102, 9/22/1944 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - Farmers View the Postwar World: A survey of the Cornbelt, the Cotton Region of the Southeast, and the Central Valley of California, 9/25/1944 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - Attitudes of Upper-Income People Toward the Investment Features of War Bond Issues, Study No. 101/Part II, 9/25/1944 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - The Fifth War Loan in the Upper-Income Market, Study No. 101--Part I, 9/27/1944 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - How City Housewives Respond to War Food Programs, 10/1944 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - Forward to the Sixth War Loan, 10/01/1944 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - What Cornbelt Farmers Think of War Food Programs, Study 102-I, 10/02/1944 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - What Farmers in the Dairy Area Think of War Food Programs, Study 105/1 (Summary Report), 10/14/1944 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Memorandum: What Housewives Eat for Breakfast, 10/16/1944 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Memorandum: Informational Sources Used by Farmers, 10/18/1944 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - Corn Belt Farmers and War Food Programs, Study 102-II, 11/1944 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - Manual: A Self-Appraisal Survey for Nutrition Committees, 11/1944 (Box 3, Folder 16)